Preliminary Guide to the AIDS Action Foundation records, 1984-2006 MS2212
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
AIDS Action Foundation records
1984-2006
1993-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
AIDS Action Foundation
MS2212
44 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, reports, articles, videocassettes, memos, meeting minutes, photographs, financial records, press releases, and early organizational records. These materials together relate the work of the AIDS Action organization both the Foundation and the Council. These records date from 1984-2006.
Historical note
AIDS Action is a national organization dedicated to the development, analysis, cultivation, and encouragement of sound policies and programs in response to the HIV epidemic. Their methods include the dissemination of information and the building and use of advocacy on behalf of all those living with and affected by HIV.
AIDS Action has been instrumental in the development and implementation of major public health policies to improve the quality of life for the estimated 850,000 - 900,000 Americans who are HIV positive. The AIDS Action Council collaborates with the greater public health community to enhance HIV prevention programs and care and treatment services; and to secure comprehensive resources to address community needs until the epidemic is over. In 1984, three years into the U.S. HIV epidemic, elected officials on Capitol Hill were inactive and silent as the epidemic's impact grew from affecting gay men in New York and San Francisco to affecting every population and community in the United States. In response to the federal government's seeming indifference, groups of volunteers organized at the local level to educate their communities on HIV prevention, to care for those living with the virus, and to grieve for those lost to AIDS-defining conditions. Yet the need remained for a national voice of authority, compassion, and reason to engage and motivate our elected officials and our country. With this in mind, a handful of the nation's first and largest community-based AIDS service organizations came together to create this voice, which they called AIDS Action.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Aids Action Foundation, 2007 (Accession 2007.019)
Arrangement
Organized into 9 series: Committee and Board of Directors, History, National Organizations Responding to AIDS (NORA), Ryan White Care Act and Ryan White Foundation, Legislation, Newspaper articles and other press, Graphics, Audio and visual materials, Other AIDS organizations
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, reports, articles, videocassettes, memos, meeting minutes, photographs, financial records, press releases, and early organizational records such as by-laws. The records in this collection present to researchers the varied methods and actions taken by AIDS Action to advocate on a national level for people living with or affected by HIV/AIDS and the organizations that serve these individuals. AIDS Action has four main strategies including informing through policy positions, connecting diverse organizations in a shared focus on HIV/AIDs, advocating to members of the United States Congress, and promoting a call to action of the nation's leaders. The records in this collection provide opportunities for researchers to observe all four strategies and analyze these efforts for the past twenty years. These records date from 1984-2006.
AIDS (Disease) -- Patients; AIDS (Disease) -- Prevention; AIDS (Disease) -- Education; Gays; Gay rights -- Washington (D.C.); Gays -- Medical care; Gay men; AIDS (Disease) -- Treatment -- United States; Gay rights; Gay men -- Washington (D.C.)
- Committees and Board of Directors, 1987-2006; Series 1; 5.75 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Organized into seven subseries: Board of Directors and Executive Committees, Communications Committee, Financial Committee, Governance Committee, Government Affairs Committee, Legal Affairs Committee, and Public Policy Committee.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains meeting minutes, reports, and correspondence related to various committees and the Board of Directors of AIDS Action. These records date from 1987-2006.
  - Board of Directors and Executive Committees, 1987-2004; Series 1 Subseries 1
    Arranged chronologically.
    This subseries contain the records of both the AIDS Action Foundation and the AIDS Action Council.
    - Council Board and Committee meetings [1/3], 1987-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Council Board and Committee meetings [2/3], 1987-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Council Board and Committee meetings [3/3], 1987-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - AIDs Action Council Board of Directors annual meeting, 1992 December 5; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board of Directors meeting, 1992 November 7; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Updates, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board of Directors, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action Council board meeting, 1995 March 18; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - annual reports and quarterly, 1995-1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action Foundation minutes, 1995 December 8; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Action Council Board of Directors meeting, 1995 December 9; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - AIDs Action Foundation Board minutes, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Council board meeting, 1996 September 7; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Action Council board meeting, 1996 December 14; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Foundation board meeting, 1996 September 6; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Board Meeting, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Board manual, 1998; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Foundation meetings, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Council minutes, 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board meeting [1/2], 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board meeting [2/2], 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Board Meeting, 1999 April 5; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Council meeting, 1999 November 20; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 1999 April 5; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 1999 July 19; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Council Board of Directors minutes, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 1999 November 20; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Council Board election, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Council and AIDS Action Foundation Board meeting [1/2], 1999 July 19; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Council and AIDS Action Foundation Board meeting [2/2], 1999 July 19; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Action Foundation minutes \5, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Board manual master, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Council Executive Committee correspondence, 1999-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 2000 November; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 2000 April; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting data [1/2], 2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting data [2/2], 2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Action Council Board meeting [1/2], 2000 August 26; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council Board meeting [2/2], 2000 August 26; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Action Council and Foundation Board meeting, 2000 April; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Council and Foundation board meetings, 2000 August; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Council Board meeting, 2001 November 17; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Council Board meeting breakout groups, 2001 April 22-23; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Action Council Executive Committee minutes, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - documents, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - council board meeting, 2001 July 21 and 2001 September 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Board of Directors meeting, 2001 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 2001 November; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2002 April 14-15; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2002 November; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Council Board of Directors quarterly meeting, 2003 January 25-26; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board of Directors meeting, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Council Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Action Council board, 2003 July 9; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board Meeting, 2003 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Action Council meeting, 2003 March; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Action Council nominations, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Action Foundation Board Meeting, 2004 January 28; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Council Board of Directors and Public Policy Committee, 2004 March 26-27; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Council Executive Committee roster, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Executive Director search committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council Board and Public Policy Meeting, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Communications Committee, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Communications Committee, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Policy briefing book for communications outreach, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Communications AIDS Action, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Financial Committee, 1996-2000; Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Finance Committee correspondence [2/2], 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Finance dues payment, 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action Foundation financial data, 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee minutes, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee correspondence [1/2], 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Governance Committee, 1992-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Governance Committee and Board, 1992-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Governance Committee minutes, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Governance Committee correspondence [1/2], 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Governance Committee correspondence [2/2], 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Government Affairs Committee, 1993-2006; Series 1 Subseries 5
    - Government Affairs Advisory Committee, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence file Government Affairs, 1997 April - December; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Governmental Affairs correspondence [2/2], 1999 March - 1998 January; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Governmental Affairs correspondence [1/2], 2000 September-1999 April; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Government Affairs meetings, 2004-2006; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Government Affairs contact list, undated; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Government Affairs Update, undated; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legal Affairs Committee, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 6
    - Legal Advisory Committee, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Public Policy Committee, 1992-2004; Series 1 Subseries 7
    - Public Policy Committee, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Public Policy Committee, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 1992 May 18-19; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Public Policy Committee co-chairs, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Public Policy Committee Internal issues, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Public Policy meeting packet, 1993 March 22-23; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Public Policy Committee misc. faxes, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Public Policy Committee, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 1993 October 25-26; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Public Policy Committee labor/HHS Senate report, 1993 September; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Public Policy Committee HCR briefing, 1993 september 2; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Public Policy Committee updated memo, 1993 July 14; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet originals, 1993 June; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 1993 June 21-22; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Public Policy Committee updated memo, 1994 March 28; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Public Policy Committee, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet, 1994 February; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Public Policy Committee Ryan White memo, 1994 January; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Public Policy Committee misc. faxes and memos, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Public Policy Committee management packet and hand-outs, 1994 November 3-4; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Public Policy Committee conference call, 1994 September 1; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Public Policy Committee fax RWCA, 1994 August 31; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Public Policy Committee Conference call packet, 1994 August 17; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Public Policy Committee mailing, 1994 August 1; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Public Policy Committee mailing, 1994 June 20; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Public Policy Committee Conference call, 1994 June 10; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet, 1994 May 24; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet, 1995 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Public Policy Committee memos, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Public Policy Committee, 1995 January 10; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting minutes, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 1995 July 23; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting packet, 1995 February 16-17; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Public Policy Committee Meeting, 1995 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Public Policy Committee legislative update, 2001 November 15; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Public Policy Committee, 2002 June 23-24; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Public Policy Committee, 2003 September; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 2003 January 26- 27; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Public Policy Committee meetings, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Public Policy Committee meetings (staff), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Public Policy Committee meeting, 2004 May 16; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Policy Continuity meeting, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Public Policy Committee immigration packet, undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Public Policy commmittee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Public Policy Committee Board Operations procedures, undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- History, 1984-2005; Series 2; 5.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, by-laws, reports, articles, surveys, polls, ballots, and subject files related to the history of AIDS Action. The material dates from 1984-2005.
  - AIDS Action Council articles of amendment, 1984-1992; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action Foundation case statement, 1987 June; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action Foundation early documents, 1989-1992; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Press conferences and other releases, 1988-1990; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations 91 AIDS related issues, 1990 October; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Nominations and Resignation, 1990-1997; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Good intentions a report on Federal AIDS prevention programs, 1991 October 1; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    General
    Prepared for AIDS Action by Helen Schietinger
  - AIDS Action Board operating policies and procedures, 1992-1994; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - By-laws, 1992-1996; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Sample of AIDS Action publications, 1992-2001; Series 2 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Watch 1993, Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Kaiser Family Foundation, 1993; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action testimony, 1993 May 6; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Pedro Zamora, 1994; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action Employment Policy Manual, 1995; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Briefing book: Negative Amendments on AIDS related issues: talking points, 1995 July; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Proposal to the Playboy Foundation, 1995 October; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action Council and Foundation early documents, 1995; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action foundation, 1996 March 15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Executive Director's Chron File [1/3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Executive Director's Chron File [2/3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Director's Chron File [3/3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Council by-laws, 1996 March; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kurt Schade, 1996; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly, 1996-1998; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Action Council Board resumes, 1997; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - State of AIDS Forum 1997 planning, Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 1997 Annual Report, series 2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - NY Event, 1997; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Communications File key / Archive key, 1997; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta regional meeting, 1997 October; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Action the National Voice on AIDS, 1997 first quarter; Series 2 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - AIDS Action Foundation rosters and terms, 1997-2000; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Action Council memorandum, 1997 October 6; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action State of AIDS Forum, 1997 July 14; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Action incoming correspondence, 1997-2001; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Action / Info Alerts, 1997; Series 2 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott, 1997-1998; series 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Name reporting and surveillance, 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lake and Associates, 1998; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Grass roots: AIDS Action alerts, 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Policy Fax Alerts, 1998 August - 1999 September; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1998 AIDS Action work plan, Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action Council / AIDS Action Foundation Archives, 1998-2002; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Action Council weekly updates, 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Action Workplan, 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Action Alert Surveys [1/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Action Alert Surveys [1/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2001; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action 1999 Organizational work plan, Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Foundation retreat Miami At the Albion, 1999; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action incoming correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - M. Joseph outgoing correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - M. Joseph outgoing correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - M. Joseph outgoing correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action Foundation outgoing correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - M. Joseph outgoing correspondence, 1999-2001; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action Foundation incoming correspondence, 1999; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - planning documents, 1999-2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2001; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000-2001; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000-2001; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action incoming correspondence, 2000-1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action prevention survey, 2000 January; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Financial Records for Andy, 2000-2001; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Sample of AIDS Action publications, 2000-2001; Series 2 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Claudia French correspondence and memos, 2000-2001; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action Council election, 2000; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Safe, Fast and Reliable a new Generation of HIV Testing, 2000; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    AIDS Action Publication
  - Regional vice chairs, 2000; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - O'Kelley Bankruptcy, 2000; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Regional testimonials, 2000; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Network News, 2000 December - 2001 July (incomplete); Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Retreat 2000 (Foundation), Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Polling, focus groups, lake materials, 2000; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising letter to George Soros, 2001; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Grant and financial information, 2001-2002; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Membership, 2001; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)